[
    {
        "front": "おおきい",
        "back": "大きい \nBig",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがく",
        "back": "大学 \nUniversity",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちいさい",
        "back": "小さい \nsmall",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "たかい",
        "back": "高い \nHigh,expensive",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "やすい",
        "back": "安い \nCheap",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "あたらしい",
        "back": "新しい \nNew",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふるい",
        "back": "古い \nOld",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ながい",
        "back": "長い \nLong",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "おおい",
        "back": "多い \nMany,much",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "すくない",
        "back": "少ない \nFew, little",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "すこし",
        "back": "少し \nA few, a little",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんぶん",
        "back": "新聞 \nNewspaper",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "はやい",
        "back": "早い \nEarly",
        "chapter": "N5 K8"
    }
]